<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>UCUI</title>
		<link>https://mrdenman-nuclear.github.io/nrcadams/</link>
		<description>NRC ADAMS Docket Update</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:15:34 GMT</pubDate>
		<lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 May 2024 23:15:34 GMT</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>https://mrdenman-nuclear.github.io/nrcadams/</docs>
		<generator>Function write_rss() in R package nrcadams</generator>
		<managingEditor>mrdenman@gmail.com</managingEditor>
		<webMaster>mrdenman@gmail.com</webMaster>
		<item>
			<title>Mod 21,extending period of performance & adding rate of payment for CY95,to "Cooperative Agreement for Radiation Monitoring Program Requirements."</title>
			<link>https://adamswebsearch2.nrc.gov/webSearch2/main.jsp?AccessionNumber=ML20082T711</link>
			<description>CONTRACTS & AMENDMENTS OR SUPPLEMENTS, TEXT-PROCUREMENT & CONTRACTS</description>
			<author>NRC OFFICE OF ADMINISTRATION (ADM), OHIO, STATE OF</author>
			<pubDate>2024-05-14 15:23:00</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Voided matls licensing action for license 42-02964-01 for Western Atlas Intl,Inc.Control:464650.</title>
			<link>https://adamswebsearch2.nrc.gov/webSearch2/main.jsp?AccessionNumber=ML20078J355</link>
			<description>DKT 30 MTL BYPRODUCT, INTERNAL OR EXTERNAL MEMORANDUM, MEMORANDUMS-CORRESPONDENCE</description>
			<author>NRC OFFICE OF INSPECTION and ENFORCEMENT (IE REGION IV)</author>
			<pubDate>2024-05-11 14:46:00</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Package of 75 comments on Reg Guide 8.18, "Info re Ensuring That Occupational Radiation Exposures at Medical Institutions Will be ALARA" & NUREG-0267, "Principles & Practices for Keeping Occupational Radiation Exposures...."</title>
			<link>https://adamswebsearch2.nrc.gov/webSearch2/main.jsp?AccessionNumber=ML20078B023</link>
			<description>CORRESPONDENCE-LETTERS, EDUCATIONAL INSTITUTION TO NRC, INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE</description>
			<author>AFFILIATION NOT ASSIGNED, AIR FORCE, DEPT. OF, ATOMIC ENERGY OF CANADA, LTD., BAYLOR COLLEGE OF MEDICINE, HOUSTON, TX, BAYSTATE MEDICAL CENTER, SPRINGFIELD, MA, CALIFORNIA, UNIV. OF, BERKELEY, CA, CALIFORNIA, UNIV. OF, SAN DIEGO, CA, CHEVRON U.S.A., INC. (FORMERLY GULF OIL CORP.), CINCINNATI, UNIV. OF, COLLEGE OF MEDICINE, CINCINNATI, CLEVELAND CLINIC FOUNDATION, CLEVELAND, OH, COLORADO STATE UNIV., FORT COLLINS, CO, CONNECTICUT, UNIV. OF, HEALTH CENTER, FARMINGTON,, DEFENSE, DEPT. OF, DEFENSE, DEPT. OF, DEFENSE NUCLEAR AGENCY, DUKE UNIV., DURHAM, NC, EMDMDTAT, ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION AGENCY, GENERAL DYNAMICS CORP., GEORGIA INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, ATLANTA, GA, GILBERT/COMMONWEALTH, INC. (FORMERLY GILBERT ASSOCIAT, HARVARD MEDICAL SCHOOL, BOSTON, MA, HAWAII, STATE OF, HEALTH and HUMAN SERVICES, DEPT. OF, HEALTH & HUMAN SERVICES, DEPT. OF, U.S. PUBLIC HEALTH, HOWARD UNIV. HOSP., WASHINGTON, DC, INTERNATIONAL BROTHERHOOD OF ELECTRICAL WORKERS, INTERNATIONAL COMMISSION ON RADIATION UNITS & MEASURE, JOHN F. KENNEDY MEDICAL CENTER, EDISON, NJ, JOHNS HOPKINS MEDICAL INSTITUTIONS, BALTIMORE, MD, LAWRENCE MEMORIAL HOSP. OF MEDFORD, MEDFORD, MA, MAYO CLINIC, ROCHESTER, MN, MEMORIAL SLOAN-KETTERING CANCER CENTER, NEW YORK,, MERCY HOSP., PITTSBURGH, PA, MINNESOTA, STATE OF, MINNESOTA, UNIV. OF, MINNEAPOLIS, MN, MISSOURI, UNIV. OF, COLUMBIA, MO, MONMOUTH MEDICAL CENTER, LONG BRANCH, NJ, NATIONAL ACADEMY OF SCIENCES, NATIONAL ELECTRICAL MANUFACTURERS ASSOCIATION, NATIONAL FIRE PROTECTION ASSOCIATION, NEW YORK UNIV. MEDICAL CENTER, NEW YORK, NY, NEW YORK, STATE OF, NUCLEAR ASSOCIATES, INC., OKLAHOMA, UNIV. OF, NORMAN, OK, ONCOLOGY THERAPY, INC., TERRE HAUTE, IN, PENNSYLVANIA, UNIV. OF, PHILADELPHIA, PA, POTTSVILLE HOSP. & WARNE CLINIC, POTTSVILLE, PA, RADIATION THERAPY & ONCOLOGY, ROCHESTER, UNIV. OF, ROCHESTER, NY, ROSWELL PARK MEMORIAL INSTITUTE, SIEMENS CORP., ST. MARY'S GENERAL HOSP., LEWISTON, ME, ST. VINCENT HOSP. & MEDICAL CENTER, PORTLAND, OR, TEMPLE UNIV., PHILADELPHIA, PA, UNIVERSITY COMMUNITY HOSP., TAMPA, FL, USAF MEDICAL CENTER, KEESLER AFB, MS, VETERANS ADMIN. HOSP., BUTLER, PA</author>
			<pubDate>2024-05-11 09:43:00</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Suppls 900831 response to Generic Ltr 88-20 re individual plant exam for severe accident vulnerabilities.Forwards NUSCO 169, "NUSCO Probablistic Safety Studies:Key Assumptions Document."</title>
			<link>https://adamswebsearch2.nrc.gov/webSearch2/main.jsp?AccessionNumber=ML20073D678</link>
			<description>CORRESPONDENCE-LETTERS, INCOMING CORRESPONDENCE</description>
			<author>NORTHEAST NUCLEAR ENERGY CO., NORTHEAST UTILITIES</author>
			<pubDate>2024-05-10 10:14:00</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Summary of 911024 meeting w/J Jones in Moab,UT to discuss NRC actions taken in response to allegation from former member of Atlas Reclamation Committee re problem of blowing dust from tailings at mill.</title>
			<link>https://adamswebsearch2.nrc.gov/webSearch2/main.jsp?AccessionNumber=ML20071L343</link>
			<description>MEETING MINUTES & NOTES--CORRESPONDENCE, MEETING SUMMARIES-INTERNAL (NON-TRANSCRIPT)</description>
			<author>NRC OFFICE OF INSPECTION and ENFORCEMENT (IE REGION IV)</author>
			<pubDate>2024-05-09 11:51:00</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>